elecok.com 2012-06-18

# Privacy Policy

## Elecok.com limited only use your information as follows:

### **Internal Use**

** **     We use your personal information to process your order and provide you with customer service. We may use your personal information internally to collect general information about visitors to this Site, improve Site content and layout, improve our outreach, and market our services and products.

### Communication with You

    We will use your personal information to communicate with you about our Site and your orders. All customers must provide an email address to allow communication with Elecok.com.com regarding orders placed. We may send you a confirmation email after you register with us as well as service-related announcements as necessary (for example, temporary suspension of service for maintenance.) You may also submit your email address to request notification when we receive a new brand, product style or product, or to sign up for our email newsletter and special offers. You can unsubscribe or opt out of future emails at any time (see the Opt Out/Corrections section below for more details).

**    We do not sell, rent, trade, license, or otherwise disclose your personal or financial information to anyone, except in the following specific situations.**

### Third-party service providers

    Like most online retailers, we sometimes use third-party service providers to perform specific functions on our behalf. Any information disclosed to them is solely to help in their provision of service. For example, we provide your name, shipping address, email and phone number to partners such as DHL and UPS in order to guarantee delivery of your orders, and we may use relevant customer information in order to monitor the quality of the third party’s service.Similarly, we must provide your credit card number to financial services organizations such as credit card processors and issuers in order to process payments. We protect all submissions of your credit card number for authorization with state-of-the-art data encryption. (More on this below in the Data Security section.)

### Legal requirement to disclose information

    We may be required to disclose information if subpoenaed, served with a court order or requested by law-enforcement officials conducting investigations, or if we are otherwise required by law to disclose such information. We will also release personal information when necessary to protect our legal rights or enforce our Terms of Use and other agreements. For example, we may share information to reduce the risk of fraud, or to prevent fraud by users who attempt fraud or other illegal activity on our Site.

### Merger and/or sale of assets

     We do not normally sell, trade or rent personal information to other companies in the course of our business. However, it is possible that we might acquire, merge with or be acquired by another company, or that we might dispose of some or all of our assets, in which case your personal information could be disclosed to another company, subject to the Privacy Notice in effect.Non-personally identifiable information: We may share information that does not identify you or any user, such as the number of daily visitors to a particular page, or the size of an order placed on a certain date, with third parties such as advertising partners.
